Guide to the Sherry Penny, Associate Provost, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Sherry Penny, associate provost, Yale University, records
1965-1979
RU 789
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
7.5
(6 boxes)
The records consist of subject files maintained by Sherry Penny as associate provost of Yale University.
Yale University. Office of the Provost
Penny, Sherry
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 3-B (YRG 3-B), Records of Yale deputy, associate, and assistant provosts.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Office of the Provost, 1992.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See inventory for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of subject files maintained by Sherry Penny as associate provost of Yale.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Office of the Provost
- Records of Sherry Penny as associate provost, 1965-1979; Accession 1992-A-057
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2014.
  - Concilium on International and Area Studies, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Economic Growth Center, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Economics Dept, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Economics, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Economics - minority graduatate program, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - office budget, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - summer term, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - summer term, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Women's Liaison Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - School of Architecture, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - School of Art, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Episcopal's move, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Divinity School, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - School of Music, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Library, 1969-1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - School of Medicine, 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Medical School: Affirmative action, 1970-1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - School of Drama, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Committee rosters, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - hotels (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - travel expenses, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Educational Policies Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Education of Women, Office of the, 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Committees on equal opportunities, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Evaluation guidelines, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Executive Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - FAS Executive Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Faculty Advisory Committee, Recruitment of Women and Minorities, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - FAS appointment memos, 1965-1974 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - faculty handbook, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - FAS Review Committee on Research involving human subjects, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Faculty spouses, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Federation of Organizations for Professional Women, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Geography, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Higher Education Resource Service, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Institutional development, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Institutional Policies Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Junior faculty summer research, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - draft search letters, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - miscellaneous, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Weaver - media design studio, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - minority administrators and faculty, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - minority students, 1972-1977 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - minority women's speakers forum, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - National Institute of Health - minority access to research careers (MARC), 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - National Institute of health - part-time fellowships, etc, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - New careers for women, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Minority students, summer programs for, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - minority summer programs, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - minority program funding (private sector), 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - New England Women Administrators (Medical School), 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - phi Theta Alpha (history honor society), 1973-1978 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Cultural exchange (Poland), 1978 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Publications from this office, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Women in Science (Schaff project), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Proposals, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Roper center, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - salary equalization, 1972-1977 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - special project: Rosabeth Hunter lecture, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Subcommittee on faculty teaching and promotion, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - subscriptions, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - summer language institute, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - summer programs, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - summer term Ford proposal, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - miscellaneous, 1974-1979 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - American Association for Higher Education newsletters, 1975-1979 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Planning Committee - New England Identification Program in Higher Education, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - American Council on Education, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Affirmative actions reports, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Afro-American Cultural Center, 1974-1978 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Association of Yale Alumni, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Bershire Conference of Women Historians, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Biology Dept research associates, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Brown University project, 1969-1977 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Center for Independent Study, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Career Advisory and Placement Service Catalyst, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Career Advisory Service move, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Career Advisory and Placement Service - general, 1974-1978 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Center for American Art and Material Culture, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Charge to a review committee, 1972-1978 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Commission on Civil Rights, 1974-1978 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Carreers, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - American Association for Affirmative Action, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Dorothy Harrison Conference, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Brown University conference, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Cornell conference, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Conference on women in science, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Associate Provost for Financial Planning - letters sent asking for nominations, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - applications for Associate Provost - short list, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Applications for Associate Provost - given to RHD
    - 1977 Jun 13 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - 1977 Jun 10 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - 1077 Jun 3 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - 1977 May 27 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - 1977 May 20 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Applications for Associate Provost, 1977 May 13 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Associate Provost search - lists of applications and nominations
    - Nominations, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - A-D, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - E-K, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - L-N, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - O-P, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - R-S, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - T-Z, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Most recent applications, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Applications - supplemented list
    - I, 1976 April 26 (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - II, 1976 April 27 (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - III, 1976 April 30 (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - IV, 1976 May 5 (Box 6, Folder 135)